Guide to the Stanford University, Institute for Diversity in the Arts, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Audiovisual materials, 1982-2008; Accession ARCH-2014-024
  - CBPA Presents: Spring Into Dance 5/23/07 (47:00), 3rd Eye Productions, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Loose discs, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - IDA Finale Performance Tape #1, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP L) (Box 9)
  - IDA Final Performance Tape #2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP L) (Box 9)
  - IDA Event Tape #1, 13 Mar 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 9)
  - IDA Event Tape #2, 13 Mar 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 9)
  - Institute for Diversity in the Arts at Stanford, Mar 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 9)
  - Cantor Tape #1, 11 Mar 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 9)
  - Cantor Tape #2, 11 Mar 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 9)
  - IDA Catalogue 01-02, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - Archive of Memory Project, 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 9)
  - Cronicas, 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 9)
  - Cronicas, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 9)
  - IDA, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 9)
  - 4 Portraits & Group Photo, Joel Simon Images, 6 Jun 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 9)
  - Stanford ReMix Project, Joel Simon Images, 2007 Mar 16; 542 computer file(s) (JPG); 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 9)
  - IDA Program, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - IDA Slide Show 2002-2008, 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - Stanford Drumming 5, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 9)
  - IDA Arts Guide Video, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 9)
  - IDA 07-08 Files (Mailing Labels/Publicity), Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - IDA 07-08 Files (FMKR Database), Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - IDA Letterhead, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - Unlabelled CD, 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 9)
  - Upward Bound: SPO1, 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Upward Bound: SPO2, 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Upward Bound: SPO3, 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA 2007: Stanford Remix, 2007 Mar 16; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA 2007: Five Disciples of John, 12 Mar 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA 2007: Black Performing Arts Cam 1, 8 Mar 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA 2007: Black Performing Arts Cam 2, 8 Mar 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cheap But Deep: Whiteness Project, 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cheap But Deep: Pat and Fed, 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cheap But Deep: Welcome to Paradise, 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cheap But Deep: Jia (Family), 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cheap But Deep: Touring Otero, 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: IDA Promo Arts Guide 2006, 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: Camera 1 – Tape 1, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: Camera 1 – Tape 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: Camera 2 – Tape 1, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: Camera 2 – Tape 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: IDA 1st Lecture, 12 Jan 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: IDA 2nd Lecture, 19 Jan 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - 2005-06 Events: IDA 3rd Lecture, 2 Feb 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Joseles De La Cruz, 21 Feb 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cantor #2415 Tape #1, 11 Mar 2008; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cantor #2415 Tape #2, 11 Mar 2008; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Cheap But Deep Final, 14 Apr 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA Event #2415 Tape #1, 13 Mar 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA Event #2415 Tape #2, 13 Mar 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - IDA Installation Exhibit/Evening Performance, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - UB Film Class, 29 Jul 2003; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Origins Rehearsal, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 9)
  - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto
    - Dreams of a City #2 (Best Copy), 31 May (1997?); 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto #8 (55:01), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto (55:00), 1997; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto (55:42), 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
    - Dreams of a City #60-#80: Green Street Party, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City #82: AIDS March #2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City #83: More Ravenswood Demolition, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City #84: Dee Uhila #1 "2 tracks – Lav + Schoeps", Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City #85: Dee Uhila #2, Georgina Peraza #1 "2 tracks – Lav + Schoeps", Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City #86: "5 minutes junk at head," Georgina Peranza [sic] #2 (00:00 – 20:50), Ravenswood Demo #3, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City #87: "Partial 9:00 min.)", Ravenswood Demolition #3, "L -/- / MP Tape 1:01:58 – 1:11:40), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City: CLIP 4/13/95, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
    - "Dreams of a City" CLIP, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto (55:00), 1997; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto (55:42), 2003 ed.; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Dreams of a City – Clip, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
    - Dreams of a City Rough Cut Selects for Ravenswood School Teachers, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
    - Dreams of a City – Clip S-VHS Master, 19 Apr 1995; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
    - Dreams of a City Rough Cut Selects for Ravenswood School Teachers, 13 Sep; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
    - East Palo Alto Project: Dancing on the Brink, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
    - East Palo Alto Project: Circle in the Dirt, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
    - Dreams of a City CBPA Submaster, 14 Feb 1997; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
    - Dreams of a City, 2003 ed.; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 3, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 4, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 5, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 6, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 7, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 8, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 9a, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 9b, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 10, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 11, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 12, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 13, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 14, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 15, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 16, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 17, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 18, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 19, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 20, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 21, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 22, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 23, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 24, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 25, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 26, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 28, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 29, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 30, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 31, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 32, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 33, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 34, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 35, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 36, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 37, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 38, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 39, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City Archive 40, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto (MASTER), 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Stanford University East Palo Alto Project: Dancing on the Brink (MASTER), Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Stanford University East Palo Alto Project: Dancing on the Brink, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Stanford University East Palo Alto Project: Circle in the Dirt (MASTER), Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
    - Stanford University East Palo Alto Project: Circle in the Dirt, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture Programs 1 & 2, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture Program 3, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture Program 4, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture Program 5, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Black Decision Makers, 1993 Apr 23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Blacks in Practical Production, 1993 Apr 30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Setting the Stage: Elements & Conditions of Black Culture, 1999 May 15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Harriet Tubman: Marcus Shelby Jazz Orchestra, 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Robert Moses' Kin: Stanford Lively Arts, 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - IDA Lecture Series 2007: Linda Tillery (59:45), 18 Jan 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - IDA Lecture Series 2007: Willie Cole (42:08), 25 Jan 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - IDA Lecture Series 2007: Jerry Quickly (59:00), 8 Feb 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - IDA Lecture Series 2007: Jon Jang (58:00), 22 Feb 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - IDA Lecture Series 2007: Aleta Hayes (58:00), 1 Mar 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - In Conversation: Judy Baca & Amalia Mesa-Bains (IDA Noontime Series), 23 Feb 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - Excerpts from 2005-2006: Resident Dialogues Butler & M. Shelby, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - Marcus Shelby Class: CBPA/Resident Dialogues, 2/28/06; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - Marcus Shelby, 3/23/06; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 10)
  - CBPA Movie, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - CBPA Presents: Circus Baoba @ Green Oaks Academy, 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - CBPA Presents: Spring into Dance, 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Sekou's Class, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Sekou's Class – 2 Interviews, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Octavia Butler, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - L'auberge du Sahel, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Pygmalion Interviews, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Resident Dialogues Presents: The Wedding Project dir. Aleta Hayes, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Wedding Project, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Wedding Project Pre-Video No Titles, Undated (Box 10)
  - Wedding Project No Titles, Undated (Box 10)
  - Wedding Project w/ Titles, Undated (Box 10)
  - Dog Eat Dog, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Boat Clinic Doc "Hardest to Reach", Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - SOS Be Veg Go Green, Undated (Box 10)
  - A Song for Jade: Just Me Productions, 2001; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Hope: Tamika Lamison, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Ravishing Raspberry: Reel Republic, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Stand Up! An Active Discourse on Civic Engagement: Council on African American Affairs, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - A Killing In Choctaw: Stanford Black Film Festival: Carl Raye, 2004; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Howard & Dave in Yosemite 5/06, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Toast Titanium 8, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Stuporwoman: Tania Isaac Dance, 16 Jun 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Allergic to Nuts: Red Wall Productions, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Loose discs, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 10)
  - Walls, 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Joe Willie's Friend: WBJR Films, 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Allergic to Nuts: Red Wall Productions, 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Fat Cake: Leslie Dektor, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Sarang Song: Tamika Miller, 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 10)
  - Setting the Stage – Richard C. Green Presentation, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture, 8-10 Oct 1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
  - Personal, Undated; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 11)
  - God's Image Carved in Ebony: Franklin & Marshall College, 11 Nov 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 11)
  - Earthling: Nation Earth, 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 11)
  - Kweli Kwa I, Undated; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 11)
  - Kweli Kwa II, Undated; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 11)
  - Unlabelled Maxell Betacam tapes, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 11)
  - Setting the Stage #1 and #2, 15 May 1999; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Black Decision Makers, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Blacks in Practical Production, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture #1 and #2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture #3, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture #4, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture #5, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture #6, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Making the Spirit of 20th & 21st Century Culture #7, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Below the Skin, 1 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 11)
  - Unlabelled 7" Reel, Undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 11)
  - Sherley Anne Williams Poetry Reading, 3 Mar 1986; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Miriam Turner Eads Interview, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - ESL Parents: Carlos Salcido and Melissa Juarez, 2 Nov 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Master Tapes from Marcus Shelby's Class, 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - IDA Series Marcus Shelby, 26 Jan 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Shelby Class Tape 1, 28 Feb 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Shelby Class Tape 2, 28 Feb 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Shelby Class Tape 1, 3 Mar 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - M. Shelby & Avenidos, 23 Mar 2006; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Willie Cole, 25 Jan 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - IDA Series Jerry Quickly, 8 Feb 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Circus Baobab, 25 May 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - IDA Lecture: Jan Jang, 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Silence, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Linda Tillery, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Interstellar Highway / Long Gone: Opiyo Okeyo, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Spring Into Dance, 23 May 2007; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 11)
  - Sanchez, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 11)
  - Gonzalez, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 11)
  - Martinez / Castoreña, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 11)
  - Rennie Harris Masterclass, 23 Oct 2000; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Paul Andrew Wandless (ZIP disk), Undated; 1 computer media (Box 11)
  - 1 – Storage Set (ZIP disk), Undated; 1 computer media (Box 11)
  - 2 – Storage Set (ZIP disk), Undated; 1 computer media (Box 11)
  - 3 – Storage Set (ZIP disk), Undated; 1 computer media (Box 11)
  - David Colón, 20 Mar 1999 (Box 11)
  - 3AQ, Undated (Box 11)
  - IDA First Person Plural Final Production, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Carthographies of Race, 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Institute for Diversity in the Arts at Stanford, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Mermaid - composed by Mark Izu, Berkeley, 1997 May 13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Below the Skin (camera 2 tape 1), 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Below the Skin (camera 1 tape 1), 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Below the Skin (camera 1 tape 2), 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - IDA Below the Skin, 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Bringing it all Back Home, 1997 Nov 8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Each One Reach One Organization, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Indian having Coffee with Kerouac, Ginsberg and Hemingway, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - The Institute for Diversity in the Arts at Stanford, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - "Real Guy/Uncle Jimmy", undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - IDA: A Multidisciplinary Artist Residency Program at Stanford University, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - IDA: A Multidisciplinary Artist Residency Program at Stanford University, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - IDA: A Multidisciplinary Artist Residency Program at Stanford University, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - AIDA Interviews, 2002 March 21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Menlo School JV Football vs. San Mateo, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Aya de Leon - Spoken Word, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - David Henry Hwag - Window Dub, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Diversity in the Arts Performance Night - Window Dub, 2002 March 15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Harry Elam/Orlando window dub, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Origins Camera 1 (window dub) - IDA show, 2004; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Origins Camera 2 (window dub) - IDA show, 2004; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Art Opening and Rosaldo, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Marc and Brenda (both tapes), undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Ollin Wide and Cutaways (window dub), 2003 March 11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - IDA First Person Plural Final Production, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - James Luna Twelve Minutes, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
- Photographs